Stuck learning new skills for months
or even years?
This video is for you. I'll give you
Let's try this again.
I think I got absolutely nothing from
that.
If you've been stuck
Learning new skills
Learning new skills. Like a muscle-up
or just skills in general?
For months or even years
This vi-
That's not very specific. If you
were to say, "If you still can't do a
muscle-up, then this video
is for you," I'm in. But that
was fucking vague, mate.
Give you my five-step framework
I don't care. What is it this video
is about?
To unlock new skills
What new skills, brother?
Faster and without spending
Bro, get to the fucking point, please
Extra hours in the gym. Step
Oh, so there's skill-based... Bro,
I don't know what this is about
One, set one specific goal. Let's
For what, brother?
What am I setting a specific goal for?
Take the strict ring muscle-up as an ex-
Okay,
so we're talking about the ring muscle-up.
Why didn't you just fucking say
that in the hook?
Are you lacking strength or
are you lacking mobility?
For example,
with the strict ring muscle-up,
you need to be able to pull to
your chest and have a deep
For this, why not just say,
"If you're struggling doing ring
muscle-ups,
try doing this. Number one,
instead of trying to do a muscle-up,
instead just build
the strength necessary to get your chest
to touch the rings." Too many people doing
a ring muscle-up don't have the strength
to do a strict chin-up, yet they're trying
to do the full thing together.
That's something where I go, oh,
do you know what?
I'm going to go into the gym,
and even though I know I can't do a ring
muscle-up,
I'm just going to try
and do ring to chest flipping chin-ups.
Yep. Then you're going to dedicate, dude
Because the information here you have
is good and needed.
It's just poorly portrayed.
Needs a bit of work, brother